

German Bulavkin

Front-end Engineer



Novi Sad, Serbia



+381621257346



thewhitehaven04@gmail.com



https://gbulavk.in



https://github.com/thewhitehaven04

Summary

Front-end engineer enthusiastic about web application performance, JavaScript language and library internals, and delivering quality software. Have a vast experience in working with international teams. Fluent in English. And my vast background in quality assurance will help you bridge the gap in understanding between development and testing.

Education

2015-2019

N.P. Ogarev Mordovia State University

Bachel's degree in Computer Science

Skills

- · Javascript/TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- React Router/Remix
- React Hook Form
- React Query
- styled-components
- Tailwind
- · Material UI
- Node.js
- Mongoose
- Jest/Vitest
- Docker

Experience

March 2024 - December 2024

— Stenn International (SME factoring)

Junior Front-end Engineer

- Development of back-office tooling for performing compliance- and fraud review
- Migrated the product's team features to the internal design system Ul kit
- Collaborated with the design team on implementation of changes to the app's design

December 2022 - February 2024

— Stenn International

QA Automation Engineer

- Conducted UI and API automated testing with Pytest
- Optimised the product team's testing practices and coverage

April 2020 - November 2022

- IBS Appline

QA Automation Engineer

- Performed UI and API testing of web- and SAP-based applications
- Refined testing policies, procedures and scripts

July 2019 - Febrary 2020

- IBS Appline

Junior QA Engineer